- 해피 추수감사절
- 안 돼, 안 돼
-Hey, everybody. Happy Thanksgiving.
-No, no, no.
올핸 추수감사절을
비밀로 하기로 했어?
Are we keeping Thanksgiving
a secret this year?
내가 배운 게임을
하고 있어
We're playing a game
I learned.
6분 안에
미국 주 이름 다 대기
You have to name all the states
in six minutes.
뭐? 식은 죽 먹기잖아
What? That's like insanely easy.
생각보다 어려워
꼭 하나가 죽어도 생각 안 나
It's harder than it sounds.
You always forget one.
때론 14개일 때도 있지
Or in some cases, 14.
멍청한 게임이고 누굴 상대로
한 게 아니니 진 건 아냐
It's stupid and I wasn't playing with
people, so technically, I didn't lose.
14개나 못 썼다고?
You forgot 14 states?
다코타 따위
누가 신경이나 써?
Nobody cares about the Dakotas!
시간 다 됐어
Okay, time's up.
난 48개
All right, I got 48.
괜찮은데, 피비는?
That's not bad. Phoebe?
주 이름 대기 싫증나서
셀러리 종류를 썼는데
I got tired of naming states,
so I listed the types of celery.
And I have one, regular celery.
하나 썼어, 일반 셀러리
So Rachel's got 48
and Phoebe has the lead in...
레이첼은 48개
피비는 야채 부문에서
vegetables. Joey?
우세하고, 조이는?
Say hello to the new champ
of Chandler's dumb states game.
챈들러의 바보 게임의
새 챔피언이 나셨다
-Wow, how many you got?
-Fifty-six.
- 몇 개나 썼는데?
- 56개
The One Where Chandler Doesn't Like Dogs
The One Where
Chandler Doesn't Like Dogs
뉴잉글랜드가
왜 주가 아냐?
Hey, how is New England not a state?
스포츠 팀도 있는데
They have a sports team.
사우스 오레곤도
스포츠 팀 있냐?
Does South Oregon have a sports team?
거 봐
There you go.
왜 자리가
하나 더 있어?
Why one extra place setting?
네 비서 초대했잖아
You invited your assistant.
그랬지, 미안해
태그 못 온대
Oh, right, sorry. Tag's not coming.
여자 친구가
만나러 왔거든
His girlfriend came into town,
so he's with her.
왜 말 안 했어?
Why didn't you tell me?
특별히 태그 걸로
고구마 호박파이 만들었는데
I made him his own
sweet potato stuffed pumpkin.
말하려고 했는데
어차피
I was going to,
but then I figured...
네 음식이야
워낙 맛있고 완벽해서
your food is so delicious
and perfect...
절대 남을 일이
없을 것 같았거든
you can never have too many
of those pumpkin things.
입에 발린 소리지만
여전히 듣기 좋다
You'd think I wouldn't enjoy that
since it's so fake, but I still do.
일반 셀러리!
Regular celery!
참 벌써 썼지
I already have that.
다 됐어
Done...
시간도 남아
with time to spare.
- 세계 신기록이야
- 잔소리 하긴 싫지만
-This may be a new world's record.
-I hate to lecture you guys...
너희같은 고학력들과
조이가 주 이름도
but it's disgraceful that
a group of well-educated adults...
다 못 댄다니
창피한 노릇이다
and Joey can't name all the states.
너희들은 지도나 그 동그란
'지구본'이란 것도 안 봐?
You ever see a map or one of those
round colorful things called a globe?
마젤란? 46개 맞았다
Magellan? You got 46 states.
- 뭐? 그럴 리가
- 46개라...
-What? That's impossible.
-Forty-six.
잘난체 하더니
10개나 빼먹어?
Well, who's well-educated now,
Mr. I-Forgot-Ten-States?
조이네 오븐 좀 켜고 올게
I'm going to go turn on Joey's oven.
조이가 음식 못 먹게
잘 감시해
Please, watch him.
Do not let Joey eat any of the food.
나 혼자 무슨 수로?
I am only one man.
- 시간 다 됐어
- 일 분만 더 줘
-Okay, time is up.
-Now, just give me another minute.
아직까지 생각 안 나면
죽어도 생각 안 나
If you don't know them by now,
you never will, okay?
그게 이 게임의 묘미지
환장할 노릇이거든
That is the beauty of this game.
It makes you want to kill yourself.
말도 안 돼
난 할 수 있어
This is crazy. I can do this.
좋아, 저녁식사 전까지
50개 다 쓴다
All right, I bet I can get
all 50 before dinner.
못 대면 저녁 없다
Okay, but if you can't, no dinner.
좋아
You're on.
내 거 보지 마라
네가 못 쓴 거 많단 말야
Don't look at my list, because there's
a lot on there that you don't have.
너희 오븐 고장난 거 알아?
Did you know your oven doesn't work?
식당 메뉴 모아둔
서랍은 멀쩡하지?
The drawer full of takeout
menus is okay, right?
오빠네 오븐 좀 쓸게
Ross, I'm gonna use yours.
챈들러, 좀 도와줘
Chandler, give me a hand.
조이, 로스가 네 아파트의
지도나 지구본 못 보게 해
Joey, do not let Ross look at maps
or the globe in your apartment.
걱정 마
미국 지구본도 아닌데...
Don't worry.
It's not a globe of the United States.
난 산책이나 할래
I'm gonna go out and take a walk.
피비, 네 가방이
움직이는데
Phoebe, why is your bag moving?
- 그럴 리가
- 정말이야, 움직여
-Oh, it's not.
-Seriously, it's moving.
- 그 안에 뭐 들었어?
- 내 뜨개질 감이야
-What the hell's in there?
-It's just my knitting. That's all.
내가 뜬 거야
Yes, I knit this.
솜씨 좋지?
I'm very good.
이 아파트 좋은데
우린 왜 여기선 안 놀까?
Ross' apartment is nice.
Why don't we hang out here?
냄새가 이상하잖아
Maybe because it smells weird.
무슨 호박 냄새
같기도 하고
It's like old pumpkins or something.
- 내 파이 냄새야
- 냄새 죽인다고
-That's my pie.
-Which smells delicious.
- 이런...
- 왜?
-Uh-oh. Uh-oh.
-What?
조이를 혼자 두고 왔잖아
We left Joey alone with the food.
그럴 줄 알았어
Yep, yep, I knew it.
저기 조이가
There he is...
개한테 음식을 먹이잖아!
feeding stuffing to a dog!
모니카와 챈들러 집입니다
여보세요?
Hi, Geller-Bing residence.
How can I help?
왜 우리 집에 개가 있지?
Why is a dog in our apartment?
죄송하지만 누구시죠?
I'm sorry, who's this?
우리 소파에
개가 앉아 있잖아
There's a dog sitting on my couch.
나 알러지 있다고 해
고소한다고!
Tell her I'm allergic, and I will sue!
- 여기 개 없는데
- 거기 있잖아!
-There's no dog here.
-There is!
얼룩무늬에
털북숭이잖아
He's black and white and shaggy.
레이첼 옆에 앉아서
손을 핥고 있네
He's sitting next to Rachel
and licking her hand.
맙소사! 너 어디 있는 거야?
Oh, my God! Where are you?
금방 갈게
I'll be right there.
벌써 왔어?
귀신이 곡할 노릇이네
They're here already?
How are they doing this?!
안녕, 태그
못 올 줄 알았는데
Hi, Tag.
What are you doing here?
아직 그 초대가 유효한가요?
I wanted to see if your offer
was still good.
그럼요, 들어와요
Well, sure. Come in.
여자 친구는 어떻게 됐어요?
Well, what happened
to your girlfriend?
오늘 아침에 헤어졌어요
We kind of broke up this morning.
- 안 됐네요
- 오하이오로 돌아갔어요
-Oh, I'm sorry.
-Yeah, so she went back to Ohio.
오하이오! 고마워요
Ohio, thank you.
개 어딨어?
Where's the dog?
무슨 개? 개 없어
What dog? There's no dog here.
그 개 갔다
Yeah, that dog left.
피비, 문 열어
Phoebe. Phoebe, open up.
여기 개 없어
There's no dog in here.
피비, 개짖는 소리가
들리는데
Phoebe, we can hear the dog barking.
No, that's just me coughing.
내가 기침한 거야
Oh, good. There you are.
마침 잘 왔다
Listen, I have a dog in my room.
있잖아
방에 개가 있지 뭐니?
What is it doing here?
개가 왜 여기 있어?
I'm watching it for friends
who left town.
친구 갠데
잠깐 봐주는 거야
Wait.
잠깐만
Hello, my name is Klunkers.
안녕하세요
클렁커예요
May I please stay
with you nice people?
친절하신 두 분
댁에 있어도 될까요?
I wish he could stay,
but Chandler's allergic.
난 괜찮지만 챈들러가
알러지가 있어
Extremely allergic, okay?
아주 심해, 알았어?
If I'm anywhere near a dog
for more than five minutes...
개 근처에 5분만 있어도
my throat will just close up.
숨을 못 쉰다니까
That's odd. This dog's been
living here for the past three days.
이상하네, 이 개 여기
3일이나 있었는데
Really?
정말?
If he's been here
that long...
그렇게 오래 있었는데도
without a reaction, maybe
you're not allergic to it.
멀쩡한 걸 보니까
얜 괜찮은가 봐
It still has to go, right?
그래도 보낼 거지?
Why?
왜?
-Okay, it's..
-Don't do it!
- 좋아, 사실은...
- 말하지 마!
-Don't do what?
-I have to.
- 뭘 말하지 마?
- 말해야 돼
Okay? It's time.
때가 왔다고
Okay, I hate dogs.
난 개를 싫어해
-What?!
-That's crazy? Why?
- 뭐?
- 말도 안 돼, 왜?
Told you.
거 봐
They are needy...
보채고
jumpy, and you can't tell
what they are thinking...
수선스럽고
속을 알 수가 없잖아
and that scares me a little bit.
그게 좀 겁나
You're right. They are scary.
맞아, 겁도 나겠다
She just ate a treat out of my hand!
내 손에서 먹이를 먹었어!
잠깐, 개는 다 싫어해?
Wait. Do you not like all dogs?
강아지도 말야
I mean, not even puppies?
강아지가 있어?
Is there a puppy here?
- 강아지도 싫어해요?
- 댁은 손님이유
-You don't like puppies?
-Okay, you are new.
챈들러, 개 얘긴
아무에게도 하지 말랬잖아
Look, Chandler, I told you. Never
tell anyone about this dog thing.
로스가 아이스크림
싫어하는 것도 그렇고
It's like Ross not liking ice cream.
- 아이스크림 싫어해?
- 너무 차단 말야!
-You don't like ice cream?
-It's too cold!
난 개가 있으면 왠지 불편해
It's just that dogs make me
a little uncomfortable.
이빨이 시려
Hurts my teeth.
너희들한텐 미안하지만
And I don't want you guys
to hate me...
도저히 저 개랑
같이 못 있겠어
but I don't think I can be around
that dog anymore, okay?
개 아니면 나
둘 중에 택해
So either the dog goes or I go.
말도 안 돼!
Oh, my God!
어떻게 이걸 모르지?
How can I not get this?
대입점수 1450 받은
대학교수인 내가 말야
I'm a college professor.
I got 1450 on my SATs.
1250이잖아
Twelve fifty.
네가 있는 걸 깜빡했다
Damn, I forgot you were here.
클렁커를 로스네
데려다 놓고
We're gonna take Klunkers to Ross'.
금방 올게
We'll be back soon.
가기 전에
한 가지만 묻자
Can I ask you a question?
여자 친구랑
헤어진 남자한테
When a guy breaks up
with his girlfriend...
얼마나 있다가 접근해야
괜찮은 거야?
what is an appropriate amount
of time to wait before making a move?
한 달 정도
I'd say about a month.
그래? 난 서너달
Really? I'd say three to four.
30분
Half-hour.
마음에 든다
Interesting.
그 남자가 비서라면
절대 안 돼지
When it's your assistant,
I'd say never.
중요한 것은
태그도 널 좋아해?
All right, Rach, the big question is,
does he like you?
그렇지 않으면
'음메' 소리나 같아
Because if he doesn't like you,
this is all a moo point.
'음메' 소리?
A "moo" point?
그래, 소의 의견이나
마찬가지라고
Yeah. It's like a cow's opinion.
아무 것도 아니란 거지
It just doesn't matter.
그냥 '음메'일 뿐이야
It's "moo."
얘랑 너무 오래 지낸 건가?
말이 되는 것 같아
Have I been living with him
for too long, or did that make sense?
조이 말 듣지 마
Don't listen to Joey.
저 남자를 봐
Okay, would you look at him?
우울하고
가족과 떨어져 있어
He's obviously depressed.
He's away from his family.
What he needs right now is
for you to be his friend.
지금 태그가
필요한 건 친구야
맞아, 미안해
그리고 고마워
You're right. I'm sorry.
Thank you.
- 좋아, 친구 돼주지 뭐
- 그래, 걔들 말 들어라
-Okay, that's what I'm going to do.
-Fine, take their advice.
아무도 내 말은
안 듣는다니까
No one ever listens to me.
겉모양이 이렇게 멋지니
내용물엔 관심도 없지
When the package is this pretty,
no one cares what's inside.
- 태그
- 레이첼
기분 어때요?
How you holding up?
괜찮아요
Not bad.
-I'm sorry about your girlfriend.
-Thanks.
- 여자 친구 얘긴 안 됐어요
- 고마워요
-Were you guys together a long time?
-A year, on and off.
- 오래 사귀었어요?
- 한 일년 쯤
I thought we'd end up together.
I don't anymore.
내 짝이라고 생각했는데
이젠 아니에요
-Now that she broke up with you.
-Yeah.
- 여자 쪽에서 찼군요
- 그래요
It's weird.
이상하죠
I used to assume that I would meet
someone and fall in love and be happy.
누군가를 만나 사랑에 빠지고
행복해지는 게
That all that was just a given.
Lately, it's like, what if it's not?
당연한 줄 알았는데
지금은 생각이 달라요
Do you ever have that feeling?
그런 생각 안 해봤어요?
No.
아뇨
Yeah.
해 봤죠
All the time.
Constantly. It's terrifying.
항상 끊임없이 하죠
너무 두려워요
But you know, then I figure
it has to work out.
그렇지만 결국은
잘 되지 않겠어요?
Why?
왜요?
Because it has to.
그래야 하니까요
-You have all the answers, don't you?
-No, no, I do. I really do.
- 뭐든 다 아는군요
- 네, 그럼요
-Thanks for talking to me.
-Come on, what are bosses for?
- 위로해줘서 고마워요
- 상사 좋다는 게 뭐예요
Hug it out.
이리 와요
All right, he likes you back.
태그도 널 좋아하는구나
Told you you should go for it.
거 봐, 시도해 보랬잖아
What?
네?
Street noise drown any of that out?
소음에 섞여
못 듣진 않았겠지?
No? See you later.
아냐? 또 보자
Okay.
그래
조이가 뭐라고 했죠?
좋아하다뇨?
What did Joey say? I like you back?
있잖아요, 사실은...
조이가 내가 등에
콤플렉스 있는 걸 아는데
Joey knows that I'm very insecure
about my back.
헌데 태그가 날 안고도
And you were hugging me...
별로 싫어하지 않으니
좋아한다고 생각한 거죠
so obviously you are not
repulsed by it. Yeah!
- 그게 아닌 것 같은데요
- 그래요?
-Wait, that doesn't make any sense.
-No?
사실대로 말할게요
All right, here's the truth.
조이 말은...
내가 태그에게
Joey said what he said...
끌린다는 거예요
because I'm attracted to you.
와
Wow.
그래요, 인정해요
Yeah, I admit it.
태그가 좋아요
직장동료라
I have a crush on you. I know that's
crazy because we work together...
안 되는 줄 알지만요
and nothing could ever happen.
태그가 당황하거나
불편해 하는 건
The last thing I wanted to do
was freak you out...
정말 원치 않아요
or make you feel uncomfortable.
무슨 말이라도 해 주면
정말 좋을 것 같네요
Which is why it would be great
if you said something right about now.
맙소사, 저 사람들
내 차 훔쳐가요
Oh, my God.
Those guys are stealing my car.
네?
What?
저거 내차예요!
Right there. That's my car!
- 이봐!
- 시간 좀 걸릴거예요
-Hey!
-Okay, that'll take one minute.
정말 나한테 지금
할 말 없어요?
Do you have anything else to say?
돌아버리겠네
I can't believe it.
말할 시간은 있어요
아직 차에도 못 탔는데
We still have time to talk,
and they're not even in the car yet.
봐요, 가잖아요
Look, there they go.
피비, 이제 가봐야겠다
Okay, Phoebe.
We should probably go back now.
가지 말아요
혼자 있기 싫어요
Please, don't leave me.
I'll be lonely.
그만해
Stop it. Stop.
- 가자, 마음 단단히 먹고
- 그래, 좋아
-Okay, let's go. We can be strong.
-Yeah, okay.
저 소리 들었어?
'모니카'라고 했잖아
Did you hear that?
She said, "Monica."
두고 못 가겠어
I can't leave her.
챈들러 모르게
다시 데리고 가자
We could sneak the dog back
and Chandler wouldn't even know.
말도 안 돼
That won't work.
3일 데리고 있어도
챈들러가 몰랐잖아
I've had that dog for three days,
and Chandler had no idea.
걘 좀 둔하잖아
He's not so smart.
야, 나도 몰랐는데
Hey. I didn't know either.
그렇지만 넌 뭔가
수상하다고 느꼈잖아
Yeah, but you kind of knew that
something was going on, didn't you?
그래, 맞아
Yeah, I knew.
챈들러 어디 있어?
Where's Chandler?
- 여기
- 손씻고 나와
-Here I am.
-Wash your hands.
어떻게 알았어?
How did you know?
개는 왜 다시 데려왔어?
Hey, what's she doing back here?
진정해
얜 아이스크림 아니니까
Relax, Ross.
She's not made of ice cream.
피비, 미국 지도를
만들어 봤거든...
Hey, look, Phoebe.
I laid out the states geographically.
시간 없어, 챈들러가
내 방에 못 들어오게 해야 돼
We don't have time.
We have to keep Chandler away.
- 그렇지만, 이거...
- 그럴 시간 없다니까!
-Yeah, but, look what..
-This is what we do not have time for!
- 모니카는?
- 피비 방에, 들어가지 마
-Where's Monica?
-ln Phoebe's room. You can't go in.
왜?
Why not?
모니카가 울어
Monica's crying.
클렁커를 보내고는
속상해서 울어
She's very upset
about this whole Klunkers thing.
- 그럼 들어가 봐야지
- 안 돼
-Well, I should go in there.
-No, no.
지금은 널 보고
싶지 않을 거야
No, she doesn't want to see
you right now.
- 왜?
- 네가 개를 보냈으니까
-Why not?
-Because you sent away the dog.
- 말도 안 돼
- 그래? 그럴까?
-That's ridiculous.
-Oh, is it? Is it?!
모니카와 내가 어렸을 때
로버란 개가 있었는데
Look, when Monica and I were kids,
we had a dog named Rover.
어느날 아버지가
개가 싫다고 하셔서
And one day, my dad decides
he doesn't like dogs.
모니카와 친구 필리스가
So Monica and her friend, Phyllis...
개를 데려갔는데
그 때 이후론 못 봤어
take away the dog and that was the
last time we ever saw him. See?
지금도 그 때와 같아
This is just like that...
몇 가지만 빼고
only with a few details changed.
좋아, 바지 갈아입었어
Okay, I'm in my sweatpants.
먹을 거 내놔
Bring on the food.
- 왜 그래?
- 개 때문에 모니카 기분이 안 좋아
-What's the matter?
-Monica's upset because of Klunkers.
그래서? 개를 데려와
그럼 넌 영웅이야
So? Bring the dog back.
You're a hero.
그래, 영웅!
그러지 뭐
Yeah, I could be a hero.
I could do that.
개가 공격하면 어쩌지?
What if it attacks me?
챈들러
개보단 큰 쥐 같잖아
Chandler, it's like a big gerbil.
그럼 겁 안 나니?
And that doesn't scare you?
로스, 도와줄까?
Ross, you need some help?
네가?
From you?
그래, 도와줘
Yes, please.
가만, 유타라니?
First of all, Utah?
막 지어내면 안 돼지
Dude, you can't just make stuff up.
미국이 싫어!
I hate America!
이 게임만 끝나면
이민가고 말거야
When I finish this game,
I swear I am moving.
- 태그, 아직 경찰서에 있어?
- 응
-Tag still talking to the police?
-Yeah.
요놈의 방정맞은 입
Dammit. Why did I open my mouth?
'난 태그가 좋아요
태그한테 끌려요'
"I have a crush on you.
I'm attracted to you."
분명 겁먹었을 거야
I know that I freaked him out.
그 목소리로 말했음 겁먹지
If you said it like that, you did.
챈들러 있어?
Hey, is Chandler here?
아니, 산책갔어
No, he went for a walk.
좋아, 비밀인데
누가 왔나 좀 봐
Okay, you cannot tell him,
but look who's back.
안 돼, 안 돼
Well, no, no, no.
챈들러가 로스네
개 데리러 갔어
He went over to Ross' to bring
the dog back here.
안 돼
개 거기 없단 말이야
Oh, no, the dog's not going
to be there!
그래?
You think?
Hi, honey.
안녕, 자기
제발 나한테 화내지 마
Please, please, please,
don't be mad at me.
- 왜? 무슨 일인데
- 얘기해 봐
-What? Why would..?
-Wait and see.
낼 수도
안 낼 수도 있어
Maybe we will, maybe we won't.
좋아, 클렁커 데려오려고
로스네 갔다가
Okay, I went over to Ross'
to bring back Klunkers for you...
문을 열어뒀더니
그새 나갔나 봐
and I left the door open,
and she must've gotten out.
옥상까지 아파트를
샅샅이 뒤져봤어
And I looked everywhere, all over
the apartment, including the roof.
그나저나 로스
누가 옥상에 대마 기르더라
Which, FYI, Ross,
one of your neighbors, growing weed.
그래도 못 찾았어
I couldn't find him...
정말, 정말 미안해
and I am so, so, so sorry.
그렇지만 고통을 없앨
방법은 알지
But I do know where we can all go
ease the pain.
좋은 소식이야
여기 좀 봐!
We have good news. Look who's back!
클렁커 아냐
맙소사!
Klunkers. Oh, my God!
- 혼자 찾아왔어
- 추수감사절 기적이야
-She came back all by herself.
-It's a Thanksgiving miracle.
이렇게 반가울 데가
It is so good to see you.
로스네 건물에서
혼자 찾아왔어
She came all the way back
from Ross'.
얼마나 힘들었을까
The things she must've seen.
비상 탈출구를 통해서
She climbed up the fire escape...
조그맣고 귀여운 발로
창문을 두드리길래 열어줬지
and tapped on the window with her
teeny paw, and we ran to let her in.
내가 과장이 좀 심했지?
I went too far, didn't I?
어디서 멈춰야 했지?
When should I have stopped?
그래, 주가 모두 50개가
안 돼서 못 맞추는 건가 봐
Okay, maybe this is so hard,
because there aren't 50 states.
내 말 들어봐
49개 주는 썼는데
Let me tell you something.
I have 49 states...
더 이상 없어!
and there are no more!
나 이제 뭐 좀
먹어도 되겠지?
I think I should be able
to eat something.
네가 알아서 해
It's up to you.
- 안녕하세요, 어때요?
- 좋아요
-Oh, hi. How are you doing?
-I'm okay.
경찰서에 가서
용의자 사진을 봐야 돼요
I got to go to the police station
and look at mug shots.
불러줘서 고마워요
Thanks for having me over.
태그, 가요?
Tag, you're going?
얘기할 기회도 없었네요
We didn't even get a chance to talk.
고향이 어디라고 그랬죠?
So where did you say
you're from again?
- 콜로라도요
- 일생에 도움이 안 돼
-Colorado.
-What good are you?
좀 전에 있었던 일
얘기 좀 해야죠
Look, I think we should talk
about what happened on the terrace.
좋아요
Okay.
해선 안 될 말을
해 버렸어요
I never should've said what I said.
내 감정 따윈
중요치 않아요
It just doesn't matter how I feel.
우린 직장 동료인데
그런 일 말도 안 되잖아요
We work together, so nothing could
ever happen between us.
월요일에 만나도 이 일은
입밖에 내지 않기로 해요
I would love to go to work on Monday
and never talk about this again.
좋아요, 월요일엔
할 일이 많죠
Okay. Big day, Monday.
Lots to do.
이제 괜찮은 거죠?
So we okay?
난 아닌데요
I'm not.
겁먹었을 줄 알았어요
I freaked you out.
겁먹지 않았어요
No, you didn't.
우리 사이 말도 안 된다는
얘기가 더 겁나는 일이죠
What freaked me out was you saying
nothing could happen between us.
- 그래요?
- 네
-Really?
-Yeah.
그러니 이런다고
해고하진 말아요
So please don't fire me
for doing this.
월요일에 할 일이
하나 줄었네요
That's one less thing
we have to do on Monday.
델라웨어였어
Delaware.
델라웨어라고
- 그래
- 나 칠면조 먹을래
-All right.
-I want my turkey now.
그래, 먹어
You got it.
네바다 두 번 썼네
You got Nevada twice.
- 알아
- 그래
-I know.
-Yeah.